Priya Nair

Software Engineer

E-Mail: npriya9976@gmail.com

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/priya-nair-1940a61b7/

Contact: (+91)8355912831

As an experienced Test Engineer, I have the capability to train other team members and carry out comprehensive reviews throughout all phases of both the Test Development Cycle and Test Cycle. My track record has shown great effectiveness as both a team leader and a collaborative team player. Additionally, I have also been responsible for overall Automated Test Execution, which proved to be immensely successful. My strength lies in Interpersonal communication, resource segregation/utilization, thorough attention to quality, planning and contributing to planning and implementing testing layouts and approaches that are efficient.

Technical Profile

- C, HTML, C++, JavaScript, DBMS, PL/SQL, Python.
- Selenium, Robot Framework.
- PyCharm, Eclipse.
- JIRA, Tricentis, Confluence.
- Jenkins, BitBucket.

Competencies

- Investigative
- Planning and Implementation
- Effective Communication
- Documentation skills
- Collaborative
- Team Management

Work History

2022-12 - Current

Automation Test Engineer at Infogain India Pvt Ltd

- Created successful test scripts to manage automated feature testing.
- Trained quality assurance team members in Test Automation execution programs and processes.
- Built automated test scripts to handle repetitive software testing work.

2021-08 - 2022-12

Automation Test Executioner at Infogain India Pvt Ltd

- Effectively Lead the Automation Execution Team and maintained Test reports for each execution cycle to improve productivity and consistency with each test cycle along with maintaining the records for Manual Test Cases and Automated Test Scripts.
- Handled Test Execution with the use of Jenkins pipeline and UltraVnc Server.
- Identified and reported any bugs found in software application by debugging the test reports and Identified and reported any bugs found in the Test Scripts by debugging the test reports and also updated the Automation Test Scripts accordingly wherever required.

2020-01 - 2021-08

Software Engineer at Infogain India Pvt Ltd

- Authored and maintained well-organized, efficient and successful manual test cases for entire team
 according to the customer requirement with minimum rework and Kept scripts and test cases updated with
 current requirements.
- Executed test scripts, logged defects and worked to resolve issues noted in testing process and monitored resolution of bugs, tested fixes and helped developers tackle on-going problems by providing QA perspective. Also debugged GUI and Comms problems and identified corrective actions.
- Led a product specific project and made strategic Test plans for consistent regression testing, vigorous new features test within a specific time frame which left ample time for AdHoc Testing, Exploratory Testing and additional Compatibility testing which led to successful completion before stipulated Deadline.

Education

Year of passing out	<u>College/School Name</u>	Examination	Marks/Grades
Pursuing(2 nd Semester)	Manipal University, Jaipur	Masters in Computer Application	7.20 (SGPA 1 st Sem)
2020	Institute of Business Studies And Research, Belapur	Bachelor's in Computer Application	7.5 (CGPA)
2017	K.V Pendharkar College, Dombivli	HSC Commerce	68%
2015	Ryan International School, Kharghar	ICSE	73%